<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>how to get free udemy course</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/</link><description>Recent content on how to get free udemy course</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tr</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free Angela Yu Python Course</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/angelaf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/angelaf/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/angelaf/angela2.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Free Angela Yu Python Course" />&lt;h1 id="how-to-buy-angela-yu-python-course-from-udemy-for-free">How to buy Angela Yu Python Course from Udemy for free&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>To get the &lt;strong>Angela Yu Python Course for free&lt;/strong> you can skip the link and access the file&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/6XlXFAb" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="best-python-course">Best Python Course&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>100 days, 1 hour a day, learn to create 1 project a day, that&amp;rsquo;s how you master Python.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>60+ hours, this Python course is without a doubt the most comprehensive Python course on the internet. Even if you have zero programming experience, this course will take you from beginner to pro. Here&amp;rsquo;s why:&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course is taught by the lead instructor of App Brewery, London&amp;rsquo;s best in-person programming Bootcamp.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course has been updated to be ready for 2022 and you&amp;rsquo;ll learn the latest tools and technologies used in big companies like Apple, Google and Netflix.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>This course cuts no corners, there are beautiful animated explanation videos and dozens of real-world projects for you to build. Tinder auto slider, Snake game, Blog Website, LinkedIn Auto Job Application Submission&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The curriculum was developed over a 2-year period with extensive student testing and feedback.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>To date, we&amp;rsquo;ve taught over 600,000 students how to code, and many have gone on to change their lives by becoming professional developers or starting their own tech startups.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>By enrolling, you&amp;rsquo;ll save over $12,000 and still have access to the same teaching materials and learn from the same instructor and curriculum as our in-person programming Bootcamp.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course is constantly updated with new content, with new projects and modules set by students - this is you!&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Free Angela Yu Udemy Flutter Course</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/dartnedir/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/dartnedir/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/dartnedir/angela.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Free Angela Yu Udemy Flutter Course" />&lt;h1 id="how-to-buy-angela-yu-flutter-course-from-udemy-for-free">How to buy Angela Yu Flutter Course from Udemy for free&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>To get the &lt;strong>Angela Yu Flutter Course for free&lt;/strong> you can skip the link and access the file&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/6XlXFAb" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="why-the-best-flutter-course-angela-yu">Why The Best Flutter Course Angela Yu&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We know you are here because you value your time. If you wanted to watch someone program for hours without explaining what they were doing, you&amp;rsquo;d be on YouTube.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By taking this course, you can rest assured that the course has been carefully thought out and organized. There are beautiful animations explaining all the difficult concepts and we are always available to answer students&amp;rsquo; questions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By the end of the course you will know the following concepts;&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Basic Flutter concepts, such as Stateful and Stateless Widgets, Widget tree, state management, animations, themes and much more.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Basic Dart concepts, such as lists, maps, enums, loops, futures, flows, mixins, classes and much more.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Object Oriented Programming (OOP) concepts: Type system, variables, functions and methods, inheritance, classes and protocols.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Control Structures: Use If/Else statements, Switch statements and logic to control the flow of execution.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Data Structures: How to work with collections such as Lists and Maps.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Software Design: How to organize and format code for readability and how to apply the Model View Controller (MVC) design pattern.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Networking: How to make asynchronous API calls, store and retrieve data from the cloud, and use JSON format for server communication.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Data Storage: How to use Firebase Cloud Firestore to act as a backend for your Flutter applications.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Authentication: How to use login and user registration for your Flutter apps.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>State Management: How to use setState, prop drilling, lifting state up, callbacks and Provider package to manage application state.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Merhaba ben Mustafa! Bu bloğu internette faydalı buldğum çeşitli yazılım hakkında bilgirendirici şeyler için kullanacağım. Her gün kontrol et!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/yuin/goldmark" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://github.com/yuin/goldmark&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/spf13/cobra" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://github.com/spf13/cobra&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/spf13/viper" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://github.com/spf13/viper&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Hugo is ideal for blogs, corporate websites, creative portfolios, online magazines, single page applications or even a website with thousands of pages.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hugo is for people who want to hand code their own website without worrying about setting up complicated runtimes, dependencies and databases.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Websites built with Hugo are extremelly fast, secure and can be deployed anywhere including, AWS, GitHub Pages, Heroku, Netlify and any other hosting provider.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Learn more and contribute on &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/gohugoio" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>GitHub&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>How To Block Ads In Spotify (Windows)</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/how-to-block-ads-in-spotify-windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/how-to-block-ads-in-spotify-windows/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/how-to-block-ads-in-spotify-windows/spotifyResim.png" alt="Featured image of post How To Block Ads In Spotify (Windows)" />&lt;h1 id="how-to-ad-block-on-spotfiy-pc-2022">How to Ad-Block on Spotfiy PC 2022&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Reklmamsız bir şekilde spotfiy deneyimi için ilk olarak verdiğim linke git.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://bcvc.xyz/Lbi9HV5" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on the links&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="ad-blocking-video-lectures-on-spotify">Ad Blocking Video Lectures on Spotify&lt;/h2>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe loading="lazy"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ION7jxKygJc"
allowfullscreen
title="YouTube Video"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>