<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on free Wordpress Themes</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on free Wordpress Themes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tr</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avada Website Builders For WordPress &amp; WooCommerce v7.8.1 free download</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-avada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-avada/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-avada/avada.webp" alt="Featured image of post Avada Website Builders For WordPress &amp; WooCommerce v7.8.1 free download" />&lt;h1 id="avada-website-builders-for-wordpress--woocommerce-v781-free-download">Avada Website Builders For WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce v7.8.1 free download&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Follow my instructions below to download Avada Website Builders For WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce v7.8.1 Free Download.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/902fe24e8d2f1609c761244f6e29bdf83dbf8a54840e6225a2bdd1066fe22a4f" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Virüs total testi Sonucu&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/Y6COre9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Porto Best Multipurpose &amp; WooCommerce Themes For WordPress v6.4.0 free download</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-porto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-porto/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-porto/porto.webp" alt="Featured image of post Porto Best Multipurpose &amp; WooCommerce Themes For WordPress v6.4.0 free download" />&lt;h1 id="porto-best-multipurpose--woocommerce-themes-for-wordpress-v640-last-version-download">Porto Best Multipurpose &amp;amp; WooCommerce Themes For WordPress v6.4.0 last version download&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>To download Porto Best Multipurpose &amp;amp; WooCommerce Themes For WordPress v6.4.0 for free, click on the link I provided and skip the ad.
The file will be there. Please let me know the links that do not work in the comment section.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/902fe24e8d2f1609c761244f6e29bdf83dbf8a54840e6225a2bdd1066fe22a4f" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Virüs total test&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/4WLmXzu" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Translated with &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.DeepL.com/Translator" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>www.DeepL.com/Translator&lt;/a> (free version)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Betheme Responsive Multi-purpose WP Theme free download v26.4.0.4</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-betheme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 06:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-betheme/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-betheme/bThema.webp" alt="Featured image of post Betheme Responsive Multi-purpose WP Theme free download v26.4.0.4" />&lt;h1 id="betheme-responsive-multi-purpose-free-download-method-v26404">Betheme Responsive Multi-purpose Free Download Method v26.4.0.4&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Betheme Responsive Multi-purpose WP Theme v26.4.0.4.0.4 Click on the link I provided to download the theme for free and skip the ad.
The file will be there. Please let me know the links that do not work in the comment section.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[# Betheme Responsive Multi-purpose Free Download Method v26.4.0.4&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Betheme Responsive Multi-purpose WP Theme v26.4.0.4.0.4 Click on the link I provided to download the theme for free and skip the ad.
The file will be there. Please let me know the links that do not work in the comment section.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/2169ff601156064c2a8d739220cd121b0dec4fcd5b3a42e92f3346161f0bba0f/detection" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Virüs total testi Sonucu&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/hnk3XyC" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Translated with &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.DeepL.com/Translator" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>www.DeepL.com/Translator&lt;/a> (free version)](&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/2169ff601156064c2a8d739220cd121b0dec4fcd5b3a42e92f3346161f0bba0f/detection" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/2169ff601156064c2a8d739220cd121b0dec4fcd5b3a42e92f3346161f0bba0f/detection&lt;/a>
)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/hnk3XyC" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Translated with &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.DeepL.com/Translator" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>www.DeepL.com/Translator&lt;/a> (free version)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Free Angela Yu Web Course on Udemy</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-web-course-on-udemy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-web-course-on-udemy/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-web-course-on-udemy/angela-web.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Free Angela Yu Web Course on Udemy" />&lt;h1 id="udemy-method-to-download-angela-yu-web-course-for-free">Udemy Method to Download Angela Yu Web Course for Free&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>If you want to download Angela Yu&amp;rsquo;s Web development course udemy for free&lt;/strong> go to the link I gave.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Skip the advert. You will see a torrent file.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Skip the ad. You will see a torrent file.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/NwajgOs" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on the link&lt;/a> skip the ad&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="best-web-course-on-udemy">Best Web Course on Udemy&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>To learn how to code and become a full-fledged web developer, you need
Complete Web Development Bootcamp, the only course that is. My Web Development course is one of the HIGHEST SCORED courses in Udemy history with over 150,000 points and a 4.8 average!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Lasting over 65 hours, this Web Development course is undoubtedly one of the
the most comprehensive web development course. Even if you have zero programming experience,
this course will take you from beginner to master. Here&amp;rsquo;s why:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course is taught by the lead instructor from App Brewery, London&amp;rsquo;s leading face-to-face programming bootcamp.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course has been updated to be ready for 2022 and you&amp;rsquo;ll learn the latest tools and technologies used in major companies like Apple, Google and Netflix.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>This course cuts no corners, there are beautifully animated explanation videos and dozens of real-world projects for you to build.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The curriculum was developed over a four-year period with extensive student testing and feedback.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve taught over a million students how to code, and many have gone on to change their lives as professional developers or by starting their own tech startups.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>You&amp;rsquo;ll save over $12,000 by enrolling, but you&amp;rsquo;ll still have access to the same teaching materials and learn from the same instructor and curriculum as our in-person programming bootcamp.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course is constantly updated with new content, with new projects and modules identified by students - that&amp;rsquo;s you!&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Through engaging video tutorials we will take you step-by-step and teach you everything you need to know to succeed as a web developer.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The course includes over 65 hours of HD video tutorials and builds on your programming knowledge as you create real-world websites and web applications.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Reviews about # Best Web Development Course&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Angela is amazing, wonderful and simply marvellous on this course. I have never had a trainer like this; she gives detailed, precise explanations in every area of the course, gives you the anxiety of learning etc. She has the ability to have fun while explaining things for better understanding. I really love this course.&amp;rdquo; - Ekeu MonkamUlrich&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Angela is very thorough without ever being boring. I have taken MANY online courses in my life, including my undergraduate and graduate degrees, and she is the best instructor I have ever had. This course is full of great instruction worth thousands of dollars and is paced well enough that anyone can pick up coding and work with it - Thanks!&amp;rdquo; - J Carlucci&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;I like the way Angela explains things, it is easy to follow and full of logic. I can tell she put a lot of energy into creating this great course. Thank you and I recommend it to anyone interested in coding!&amp;rdquo; - Yiqing Zheng&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;So far (on my third day) this course has taught me more than I have learnt in many other programming courses. This course builds on itself gradually in a clearly summarised and easy to understand way.&amp;rdquo; - Normal Ramsey&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;This course will really take you from beginner to intermediate level. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to put the pieces of web development together this is what you are looking for. Angela does a great job explaining the concepts in real practice, creating projects throughout this course. Thank you so much, Angela. I will always consider you as my mentor and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to take more courses with you.&amp;rdquo; - Moises Dionisio Cruz&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Great course, perfect for absolute beginners at the beginning of their coding journey! Angela is a great instructor and is able to explain even complex coding concepts in the most simple and understandable way. Learning web development doesn&amp;rsquo;t get more fun than this!&amp;rdquo; - Zoe Moyssoglou&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;A different approach to Web Development training. I love that you are given everything possible to succeed right from the start.&amp;rdquo; - Ronick Thomas&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The teacher is simply AMAZING, the best teacher I have ever had. I would give him 10 out of 5 stars. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t just punch the code and talk to himself, but he actually explains things. He keeps giving really helpful tips and will give you lots of other references. I always knew what I was doing and why I was doing it. All the extra challenges made me remember and understand things better. - Peter Dlugos&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Free Angela Yu Python Course</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-python-course/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-python-course/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-python-course/angela2.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Free Angela Yu Python Course" />&lt;h1 id="how-to-buy-angela-yu-python-course-from-udemy-for-free">How to buy Angela Yu Python Course from Udemy for free&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>To get the &lt;strong>Angela Yu Python Course for free&lt;/strong> you can skip the link and access the file&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/6XlXFAb" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="best-python-course">Best Python Course&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>100 days, 1 hour a day, learn to create 1 project a day, that&amp;rsquo;s how you master Python.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>60+ hours, this Python course is without a doubt the most comprehensive Python course on the internet. Even if you have zero programming experience, this course will take you from beginner to pro. Here&amp;rsquo;s why:&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course is taught by the lead instructor of App Brewery, London&amp;rsquo;s best in-person programming Bootcamp.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course has been updated to be ready for 2022 and you&amp;rsquo;ll learn the latest tools and technologies used in big companies like Apple, Google and Netflix.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>This course cuts no corners, there are beautiful animated explanation videos and dozens of real-world projects for you to build. Tinder auto slider, Snake game, Blog Website, LinkedIn Auto Job Application Submission&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The curriculum was developed over a 2-year period with extensive student testing and feedback.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>To date, we&amp;rsquo;ve taught over 600,000 students how to code, and many have gone on to change their lives by becoming professional developers or starting their own tech startups.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>By enrolling, you&amp;rsquo;ll save over $12,000 and still have access to the same teaching materials and learn from the same instructor and curriculum as our in-person programming Bootcamp.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The course is constantly updated with new content, with new projects and modules set by students - this is you!&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Free Angela Yu Udemy Flutter Course</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-udemy-flutter-course/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-udemy-flutter-course/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/free-angela-yu-udemy-flutter-course/angela.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Free Angela Yu Udemy Flutter Course" />&lt;h1 id="how-to-buy-angela-yu-flutter-course-from-udemy-for-free">How to buy Angela Yu Flutter Course from Udemy for free&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>To get the &lt;strong>Angela Yu Flutter Course for free&lt;/strong> you can skip the link and access the file&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://bc.vc/6XlXFAb" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on link&lt;/a> skip ad&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="why-the-best-flutter-course-angela-yu">Why The Best Flutter Course Angela Yu&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We know you are here because you value your time. If you wanted to watch someone program for hours without explaining what they were doing, you&amp;rsquo;d be on YouTube.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By taking this course, you can rest assured that the course has been carefully thought out and organized. There are beautiful animations explaining all the difficult concepts and we are always available to answer students&amp;rsquo; questions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By the end of the course you will know the following concepts;&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Basic Flutter concepts, such as Stateful and Stateless Widgets, Widget tree, state management, animations, themes and much more.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Basic Dart concepts, such as lists, maps, enums, loops, futures, flows, mixins, classes and much more.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Object Oriented Programming (OOP) concepts: Type system, variables, functions and methods, inheritance, classes and protocols.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Control Structures: Use If/Else statements, Switch statements and logic to control the flow of execution.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Data Structures: How to work with collections such as Lists and Maps.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Software Design: How to organize and format code for readability and how to apply the Model View Controller (MVC) design pattern.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Networking: How to make asynchronous API calls, store and retrieve data from the cloud, and use JSON format for server communication.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Data Storage: How to use Firebase Cloud Firestore to act as a backend for your Flutter applications.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Authentication: How to use login and user registration for your Flutter apps.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>State Management: How to use setState, prop drilling, lifting state up, callbacks and Provider package to manage application state.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>How To Block Ads In Spotify (Windows) 2022</title><link>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/how-to-block-ads-in-spotify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/how-to-block-ads-in-spotify/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://mryuksel101.github.io/en/p/how-to-block-ads-in-spotify/spotifyResim.png" alt="Featured image of post How To Block Ads In Spotify (Windows) 2022" />&lt;h1 id="how-to-ad-block-on-spotfiy-pc-2022">How to Ad-Block on Spotfiy PC 2022&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Pour une expérience spotfiy sans publicité, allez d&amp;rsquo;abord sur le lien que j&amp;rsquo;ai fourni.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://bcvc.xyz/Lbi9HV5" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Click on the links&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="ad-blocking-video-lectures-on-spotify">Ad Blocking Video Lectures on Spotify&lt;/h1>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe loading="lazy"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ION7jxKygJc"
allowfullscreen
title="YouTube Video"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>